

CONTACT

P: +62 83857663508 E: vincent.kenny98@gmail.com W: vincentkenny.github.io L: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kennyvincent-831282199/

Currently based in Jakarta, Indonesia

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Web programming - Backend Web programming - Frontend Desktop app programming

PERSONAL TRAITS

Organized
Reliable and professional
Team player
Fast learner
Excellent communication
Punctual

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Java - Springboot PHP - Codelgniter C# - DotNet Core SQL - PL/SQL JavaScript -Angular

FAMILIAR TECHS AND TOOLS

GIT
Jenkins
Kafka
Redis
Postgres
Tought Machine's Vault

KENNY VINCENT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER ABOUT

I am an IT professional with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science. I am experienced in developing web applications and desktop applications on an enterprise scale. I am passionate about learning new things and solving problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR BACKEND DEVELOPER

Ajaib Sekuritas Asia | Jun 2022 - Present (Link) Ajaib is an investment super-app that allows user to buy mutual funds, publicly traded stocks, and cryptocurrency.

- Developing backend web services using Springboot to facilitate customer onboarding process using caching and streaming messages using redis and kafka.
- Developing core banking products using Thought Machine's Vault to enable the usage of new products for a digital bank e.g. CASA account, Fixed deposit, etc.
- Doing PR reviews for other engineers both senior and associate level to ensure code quality are up to standards set by the company and satisfy product requirements
- Writing tech specs and documentation regarding services development to be used by other engineers as reference before the hands-on coding process.

IT SPECIALIST - FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Bank Central Asia | Jan 2021 - Jun 2022 (Link)
BCA is the biggest non-government owned Bank in Indonesia

- Developed backend web services using Springboot
- Developed stored procedures and maintaining databases using Oracle
- Developed frontend web applications using Angular
- Developed desktop applications using Dot Net Core
- Contributed on development plans for projects
- Maintaining systems that are used nationally.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

INSTITUT SAINS DAN TEKNOLOGI TERPADU SURABAYA | 2016 - 2020 GPA 3.80 / 4.00 (Link)

Publications

Universal Face Recognition Using Multiple Deep Learning Agent and Lazy Learning Algorithm

Vincent, K.,& Kristian, Y. (2021). Universal face recognition using multiple deep learning agent and lazy learning algorithm. *COMMIT JOURNAL*, 15(2),

https://journal.binus.ac.id/index.php/commit/article/view/6688